{
    "subject": "resource/Equestrian_at_the_1924_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Team_jumping",
    "predicate": "ontology/silverMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Hans_von_der_Weid",
    "human_readable": "Hans von der Weid won the silver medal in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.982973575592041,
            "question": "Who won the silver medal in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9511893391609192,
            "question": "What event did Hans von der Weid compete in at the 1924 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9250859618186951,
            "question": "In what year did Hans von der Weid win a silver medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8791704773902893,
            "question": "At which Olympic Games did Hans von der Weid win a medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.853523850440979,
            "question": "What type of sport was team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7322891354560852,
            "question": "What color medal did Hans von der Weid win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6537360548973083,
            "question": "Did Hans von der Weid win any other medals at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5113831162452698,
            "question": "Was Hans von der Weid competing individually or as part of a team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4824103116989136,
            "question": "Are there any other notable athletes who competed in the 1924 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13881686329841614,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges associated with team jumping?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hans von der Weid won the silver medal in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6262_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable athletes who competed in the 1924 Summer Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6262_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Hans von der Weid competing individually or as part of a team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6262_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Hans von der Weid win any other medals at the Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6262_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6262_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe documents do not mention Hans von der Weid, and therefore do not provide any information about his achievements or awards."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information about Hans von der Weid or his achievements in the 1924 Summer Olympics, specifically regarding a silver medal in team jumping. The documents discuss various Olympic events and medals won by different countries and athletes but do not mention this specific individual or event."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Hans von der Weid in the context information provided.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Hans von der Weid winning a medal in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics in any of the provided text.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The list of Olympic bronze medal winners from the 1924 Summer Olympics mentioned in context information 6 does not include Hans von der Weid, but rather athletes such as Eric Liddell and Frank Beaurepaire.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "There is no information supporting Hans von der Weid winning a silver medal in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics. The provided context lists medal winners for various events, but does not include a record of this specific achievement by Hans von der Weid.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}